<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ~</title>
    <link>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ~</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 15:12:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Git For Newbies</title>
      <link>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 15:12:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/three/</guid>
      <description>Before we start make sure git --version command successfully returns. If the output is something like command not found then please make sure Git is properly installed on your machine. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed git then download from this Git Link My machine output is shown below. Output on your machine might be different.
 Commands that a user should type on his/her terminal are prefixed with the shell prompt symbol $.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rename a local and remote branch in git</title>
      <link>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 14:19:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/post/</guid>
      <description>if you have named a branch incorrectly and pushed to the remote repository or more precisely if you think you have messed up then follow this steps
1.) Rename your local branch If you are on the branch you want to rename:
git branch -m new-name if you are on different branch
git branch -m old-name new-name 2.) Delete the old-name remote branch and push the new-name local branch git push origin :old-name new-name 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kryptocodes.github.io/posts/two/</guid>
      <description>Today Open source software is used by everyone and everywhere knowingly or unknowingly but it was not like this from the beginning
Blah blah it all started somewhere and now we are here
Smells like open source
Android ? prolly you would be using android device right now ? welp that&amp;rsquo;s a Open source
So what is Open source? Open Source is a term denoting that product includes permission to use its source code, design documents,or content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>